Finding Aid for the Peter H. Prince Papers MS.2921
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Research Files, 1770-2006; I
  - Photographs, 1838-2006 (bulk 1884-2005); J
    - Little Cataloochee: J. V. Tine Woody Gravestone, 1994 October 17 (Box 31, Folder 95)
    - Little Cataloochee: Mack W. Hannah Gravestone, 1984 October 17 (Box 31, Folder 96)
    - Little Cataloochee: L. E. Smith Gravestone, 1994 October 17 (Box 31, Folder 97)
    - Little Cataloochee: Logan Hannah Gravestone, 1994 October 17 (Box 31, Folder 98)
    - Little Cataloochee: John Jackson Hannah Gravestone, 1994 October 17 (Box 31, Folder 99)
    - Little Cataloochee: Nick W. Hannah Gravestone, 1994 October 17 (Box 31, Folder 100)
    - Little Cataloochee: Little Cataloochee School, 1937 December 1 (Box 31, Folder 101)
    - Little Cataloochee: Ras and Alice Hannah Still Site, 1937 May 14 (Box 31, Folder 102)
    - Little Cataloochee: Cook Place Apple Barn, 1999 October 24 (Box 31, Folder 103)
    - Little Cataloochee: Mary Jenkins Grave, 1987 May 21 (Box 31, Folder 104)
    - Little Cataloochee: John Jackson Hannah Log Cabin, 1999 October 24 (Box 31, Folder 105)
    - Little Cataloochee: Daniel J. Cook Cabin, 1999 October 24 (Box 31, Folder 106)
    - Little Cataloochee: Little Cataloochee Baptist Church, 1987 May 21 (Box 31, Folder 107)
    - Bishop Francis Asbury: Bishop Francis Asbury, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 108)
    - Mount Sterling: Carolina Power, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 109)
    - Mount Sterling: A. W. Hopkins Mill and Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad, undated (Box 31, Folder 110)
    - Mount Sterling: A. W. Hopkins Overshot Grist Mill, 1923 November 20 (Box 31, Folder 111)
    - Mount Sterling: Benjamin R. Hopkins, undated (Box 31, Folder 112)
    - Mount Sterling: Meal Sack at the A. W. Hopkins Mill, undated (Box 31, Folder 113)
    - Mount Sterling: Boys Herding Calves, 1931 May 17, 1981 May 6 (Box 31, Folder 114)
    - Mount Sterling: Reuben P. Clark General Store, undated (Box 31, Folder 115)
    - Mount Sterling: Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad Construction, 1902 February 13 (Box 31, Folder 116)
    - Mount Sterling: Mount Sterling Tower, 1951 June 3 (Box 31, Folder 117)
    - Mount Sterling: John McCarter Cabin, 1935 (Box 31, Folder 118)
    - Mount Sterling: Sage Sutton Gravestone, 1994 May 13 (Box 31, Folder 119)
    - Mount Sterling: Millstones in Sutton Mill Foundation, 1994 May 13 (Box 31, Folder 120)
    - Mount Sterling: Hilliard McGaha Gravestone, 1994 May 13 (Box 31, Folder 121)
    - Mount Sterling: Mount Sterling Post Office, undated (Box 31, Folder 122)
    - Mount Sterling: A. W. Hopkins Home, 1914 (Box 31, Folder 123)
    - Mount Sterling: Allison W. Hopkins and Elizabeth Hopkins, undated (Box 31, Folder 124)
    - Mount Sterling: Allison W. and Elizabeth Hopkins, undated (Box 31, Folder 125)
    - Mount Sterling: Mary Harrell and Josie Sutton, undated (Box 31, Folder 126)
    - Mount Sterling: Leatherwood Gentlemen, 1918 (Box 31, Folder 127)
    - Mount Sterling: Mount Sterling Methodist Church, 1920 (Box 31, Folder 128)
    - Mount Sterling: Cherokee Workers Building the Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad, 1902 (Box 31, Folder 129)
    - Mount Sterling: Llamas in the Great Smoky Mountains National Park, 2004 March 19 (Box 31, Folder 130)
    - Mount Sterling: Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad, 1910 May 15 (Box 31, Folder 131)
    - Mount Sterling: John Croxier Hopkins House, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 132)
    - Crestmont: Hart Avenue, undated (Box 31, Folder 133)
    - Crestmont: Hart Street, 1910 (Box 31, Folder 134)
    - Crestmont: Crestmont, 1911 (Box 31, Folder 135)
    - Crestmont: Lacy Street, undated (Box 31, Folder 136)
    - Crestmont: Dr. Walter McMahan, 1911 (Box 31, Folder 137)
    - Crestmont: Dr. McMahan and Convicts on the Railroad, 1911 June 18 (Box 31, Folder 138)
    - Crestmont: Champion Lumber Employee Housing, 1912 (Box 31, Folder 139)
    - Crestmont: Nellie Hicks Gravestone, 1994 May 13 (Box 31, Folder 140)
    - Crestmont: Crestmont Sunday School, 1913 (Box 31, Folder 141)
    - Crestmont: Lina Nuckles, 1914 (Box 31, Folder 142)
    - Crestmont: Big Creek Bridge, 1912 (Box 31, Folder 143)
    - Crestmont: Boarding House, 1912 (Box 31, Folder 144)
    - Crestmont: Woodland Theater, 1912 (Box 31, Folder 145)
    - Crestmont: Connie Leatherwood, 1928 (Box 31, Folder 146)
    - Crestmont: Robert F. Whitmire, 1913 (Box 31, Folder 147)
    - Crestmont: Crestmont (Formerly Mount Sterling), undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 31, Folder 148)
    - Crestmont: Max Patch and Lodge, undated (Box 31, Folder 149)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Building Railroad Bridge, 1902 (Box 31, Folder 150)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Mount Sterling Passenger Station, 1903 March 6 (Box 31, Folder 151)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Crestmont Passenger Station, 1909 January 1 (Box 31, Folder 152)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Crestmont, 1908, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 153)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Crestmont, 1908 (Box 31, Folder 154)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Champion Lumber Company, 1913 (Box 31, Folder 155)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Pigeon River Bridge, 1901 (Box 31, Folder 156)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Tennessee and North Carolina Railroad, 1912 (Box 31, Folder 157)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Ledgerwood Skidder, 1913 (Box 31, Folder 158)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Champion Lumber Shay Engine #6, 1912 (Box 31, Folder 159)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Midnight Hole Trestle, 1911 (Box 31, Folder 160)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Max Patch Railroad (1917-1931), undated (Box 31, Folder 161)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Max Patch Lodge, 1930, 1934 April 6 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Max Patch (4629'), 1926 June 22 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Rail Passenger Bus, 1927 April 19, 1936 June 15 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Railroad Timetable, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Lima Engine #102, 1913 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad: Lima Engine #2, 1906 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Champion Lumber Company: Mill at Crestmont, 1911 December 21 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Champion Lumber Company: Crestmont Mill, 1913 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Champion Lumber Company: Climax Locomotive #311, 1914 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Champion Lumber Company: Crestmont Town Hall, 1913 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Champion Lumber Company: Big Creek Mill, 1910 May 15 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Champion Lumber Company: Planing Mill, 1913 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Champion Lumber Company: Clyde Ground Skidder, 1913 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Champion Lumber Company: Sorting Dock, 1913 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Champion Lumber Company: Mill and Tennessee & North Carolina Railroad, 1912 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Champion Lumber Company: Mouse Creek Falls (Crossed by Railroad in 1906), 2003 February 16 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Champion Lumber Company: Sinking Creek Logging Camp, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Champion Lumber Company: Walnut Bottom, 1911 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Davenport Gap: Colonel William Davenport Gravestone, 1996 May 10 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Davenport Gap: Tennessee-North Carolina Survey Marker (erected 1821), undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Davenport Gap: Mount Cammerer Lookout Tower, 1940 December 15 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Davenport Gap: Mount Cammerer, 1940 November 24 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Davenport Gap: Mount Cammerer Tower, undated (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Davenport Gap: White Rock, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Davenport Gap: Mount Cammerer Lookout Tower, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Max Patch: Little Tennessee River Ferry, 2005 December (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Max Patch: Nancy Ghormley Gravestone, 1993 May 1 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Max Patch: Hugh Ghormley Gravestone, 1993 May 1 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Max Patch: Bas Shaw Gravestone, 1993 May 1 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Max Patch: Bas Shaw Gravestone, 1993 May 1 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Max Patch: Primitive Camp on Abrams Creek, 1902 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Max Patch: View of the Great Smoky Mountains, 1896 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Max Patch: Crossing Historic Abrams Creek, 1902 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Max Patch: Swimming in the Little Tennessee River, 1902 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Max Patch: Delivering Mail, undated (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Max Patch: St. James Episcopal Church, 1998 August 3; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 81, Folder 5] (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Max Patch: St. James Episcopal Church, 1998 August 3 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Max Patch: Sultana Steamboat Disaster Monument, 2003 September 6 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Max Patch: Bas Shaw Gravestone, 1987 June 8, 1996-1998; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 82, Folder 1] (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Engine #908 en route to Calderwood, 1929 March 10, 2004-2005 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Babcock Trestle, 1915 July 4 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Chilhowee Depot, 1929 August (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Babcock Trestle, undated; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 90, Folder 3] (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Citico & Grand Forks Railroad, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Tapoco Railroad Engine #3, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Schedule, 1928 December 2 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Albert E. Boone, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Knoxville & Augusta Railway Station in Maryville, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Blue Ridge Railroad (includes the Knoxville & Charleston Railroad) Stock, 1869 July 1 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Blue Ridge $4 Million Loan], undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Stumphouse Railroad Tunnel (built 1853), 2003 August 8 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Stumphouse Railroad Tunnel, 1968 May 1 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Sultana Disaster, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Little River Norfolk Southern Trestle, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Knoxville & Charleston Piers, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Summers at Sunline Ferry on the Little Tennessee River, 1914 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Girls Playing at Sunline Ferry on the Little Tennessee River, circa 1914 (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Sunline Ferry on the Little Tennessee River, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Sunline Ferry, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Swimmers at Sunline Ferry, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Sunline Ferry Railroad Stop, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Joshua H. Jones House, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Girls and Oxen at Sunline Ferry, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Family at Sunline, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Sunline, 1914 (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Picnicers on the Little Tennessee River, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Little River Railroad Construction, undated (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Railway Crew at Calderwood, 1925 (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Montvale Station, undated (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Blount and Knox County Bridges on the Blue Ridge Railroad, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 32, Folder 70)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Tracklayers in Calderwood, 1916 March 1 (Box 32, Folder 71)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Sam Brooks Tram Railroad, 1935 (Box 32, Folder 72)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Babcock Trestle on the Little Tennessee River, 1996 January 2 (Box 32, Folder 73)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Babcock Lumber & Land Company, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 74)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Babcock Railroad Trestle, 1996 January 2 (Box 32, Folder 75)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Railway Tunnel Canyon (dug 1856), 2003 March 6 (Box 32, Folder 76)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Tallassee Power Company Heisler #9, 1918 (Box 32, Folder 77)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Tallassee Power Company Railroad, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 78)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Calderwood Dam Construction, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 79)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Tallassee Power Company Steam Engine, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 80)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Tallassee Power Company Engine #9, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 32, Folder 81)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: No. 2006 Porter Steam Engine, circa 1930s (Box 32, Folder 82)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Shop Creek Derailment, 1916 March 1 (Box 32, Folder 83)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Track Layers in Calderwood, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 84)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: ALCOA Railroad Mail Car, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 85)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: U. S. Highway 129 Bridges (Abrams Creek and Chilhowee Dam), 1940 (Box 32, Folder 86)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Ike Branch Logging Camp, undated (Box 32, Folder 87)
    - Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad: Babcock Land & Lumber Company Sawmill at Alcoa, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 88)
    - Parsons Turnpike: Parsons Turnpike, circa 1902; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 82, Folder 2] (Box 32, Folder 89)
    - Parsons Turnpike: Joshua Parsons' Gravesite, 1995 November 9; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 82, Folder 3] (Box 32, Folder 90)
    - Parsons Turnpike: Railroad Tunnel, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 32, Folder 91)
    - Parsons Turnpike: Parsons Turnpike, 1996 February 13 (Box 32, Folder 92)
    - Parsons Turnpike: Tollgate, 1898; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 82, Folder 4] (Box 32, Folder 93)
    - Parsons Turnpike: Historical Marker, undated (Box 32, Folder 94)
    - Parsons Turnpike: Tollgate and Historical Marker, undated (Box 32, Folder 95)
    - Parsons Turnpike: Travelers in Carriage, 1902 (Box 32, Folder 96)
    - Parsons Turnpike: Tollgate Marker, undated (Box 32, Folder 97)
    - Chilhowee: Schenectady Engine #908 (Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad), 1926; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 82, Folder 5 and Box Space 83] (Box 32, Folder 98)
    - Chilhowee: City Lady in the Smokies, circa 1890s (Box 32, Folder 99)
    - Chilhowee: Tallassee Ferry, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 100)
    - Chilhowee: Little Tennessee Ferry, 1936 April 5 (Box 32, Folder 101)
    - Chilhowee: St. Andrews Episcopal Church, 1998 October 14 (Box 32, Folder 102)
    - Chilhowee: Panther Creek Falls, 1896 (Box 32, Folder 103)
    - Chilhowee: Little Tennessee River, circa 1890s (Box 32, Folder 104)
    - Chilhowee: Pleasant Henry House, undated (Box 32, Folder 105)
    - Chilhowee: Abrams Creek, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 106)
    - Chilhowee: Chilogatee Branch Overshot Mill, 1901 (Box 32, Folder 107)
    - Chilhowee: Tellico River Lumber, undated (Box 32, Folder 108)
    - Chilhowee: Alva and May Lawson McGhee, circa 1900s (Box 32, Folder 109)
    - Chilhowee: Whitehead Cemetery, 1996 February 13 (Box 32, Folder 110)
    - Chilhowee: Calderwood, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 111)
    - Chilhowee: View on the Little Tennessee River, 1944 March 11 (Box 32, Folder 112)
    - Chilhowee: Rebecca Shaw (widow of Bas Shaw) Gravesite, 1996 October 21 (Box 32, Folder 113)
    - Chilhowee: North Carolina Travelers, 1902 (Box 32, Folder 114)
    - Chilhowee: Harvey S. Bright Home, 1902 (Box 32, Folder 115)
    - Chilhowee: Handmade Wheat Shocks, 1902; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 84, Folder 1] (Box 32, Folder 116)
    - Chilhowee: Montvale Spring Hotel Staircase, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 117)
    - Chilhowee: Tallassee Inn, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 32, Folder 118)
    - Chilhowee: Chimney Gate Toll House on Parsons Turnpike, 2004 March 13 (Box 32, Folder 119)
    - Chilhowee: Parson W. G. Brownlow, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 120)
    - Richwood: Richwood School, 1920 (Box 32, Folder 121)
    - Richwood: Richwood (established 1873), 1994 (Box 32, Folder 122)
    - Richwood: Richwood School and Church, 1938 January, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 123)
    - Richwood: Tom Boring Turbine Mill, undated (Box 32, Folder 124)
    - Slate Mines: Colonel William D. Hamilton Flour Mill, 1902 (Box 32, Folder 125)
    - Slate Mines: Wildham Post Office, undated (Box 32, Folder 126)
    - Slate Mines: Colonel William D. Hamilton House, 1902 (Box 32, Folder 127)
    - Slate Mines: Hamilton Slate Quarry, 1902, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 128)
    - Slate Mines: Slate Quarry Railroad, 1905 (Box 32, Folder 129)
    - Look Rock: Eli Caylor Gravesite, 2005 October 17 (Box 32, Folder 130)
    - Look Rock: Garner Family, 1896, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 131)
    - Look Rock: Garner Family, 1896; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 84, Folder 2] (Box 32, Folder 132)
    - Look Rock: Dr. Felix Oswald's Monkey House, 1896 (Box 32, Folder 133)
    - Look Rock: Look Rock Tower, 1996 April 14 (Box 32, Folder 134)
    - Look Rock: Montvale Springs Hotel (shown circa 1871), 1993 December 10 (Box 32, Folder 135)
    - Look Rock: The Spring House, Montvale Spring Hotel, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 136)
    - Look Rock: Look Rock Crevice, 1896, 1996 April 14 (Box 32, Folder 137)
    - Look Rock: Look Rock Tower, 1996 April 14 (Box 32, Folder 138)
    - Gregory Bald: Sunset, 1901 (Box 32, Folder 139)
    - Gregory Bald: Big Bald Mountain (Now Gregory Bald), 1886 August 27 (Box 32, Folder 140)
      Scope and Contents Note
      Note: The photographer's name should be William Cox Cochran, not William C. Chumlea.
    - Gregory Bald: Early Hikers, 1886 August 27 (Box 32, Folder 141)
    - Gregory Bald: Russell Gregory Place, 1901 (Box 32, Folder 142)
    - Gregory Bald: Gregory Bald from Cades Cove, 1934 October 7 (Box 32, Folder 143)
    - Gregory Bald: Sheep Grazing on Gregory Bald, undated (Box 32, Folder 144)
    - Gregory Bald: Russell Gregory, 1999, 2005; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 84, Folder 3] (Box 32, Folder 145)
    - Gregory Bald: Russell Gregory's Grave, 1994 July 8 (Box 32, Folder 146)
    - Cades Cove: Development Warning Sign, undated (Box 32, Folder 147)
    - Cades Cove: Cades Cove, 1934-1949 (Box 32, Folder 148)
    - Cades Cove: Thunderhead Mountain (5527'), 1951 October 22, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 149)
    - Cades Cove: Abrams Falls (Jesse Dempster Diving), 1941 August 3; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 84, Folder 4] (Box 32, Folder 150)
    - Cades Cove: John P. Cable Mill, 1961 December 29-31; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 84, Folders 5-6] (Box 32, Folder 151)
    - Cades Cove: Abrams Falls (Charles Roth Diving), 1937 August 8 (Box 32, Folder 152)
    - Cades Cove: Daniel Bird Lawson House, 1886 August 25 (Box 32, Folder 153)
    - Cades Cove: John Oliver Place, 1936 August 23 (Box 32, Folder 154)
    - Cades Cove: Cades Cove Missionary Baptist Church, 1989 May 21 (Box 32, Folder 155)
    - Cades Cove: John Oliver Place, 1967 June (Box 32, Folder 156)
    - Cades Cove: Elie Caylor Gravesite, 2005 October 17 (Box 32, Folder 157)
    - Cades Cove: James Spence Gravesite, 2005 October 17 (Box 32, Folder 158)
    - Cades Cove: Baptism in Abrams Creek, 1920 August 7 (Box 32, Folder 159)
    - Cades Cove: Wheat Threshers, 1903; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 85, Folder 1] (Box 32, Folder 160)
    - Cades Cove: McCampbell Knob (4480') from Cades Cove, 1961 December 29; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 85, Folder 2] (Box 32, Folder 161)
    - Cades Cove: Hamp Tipton Corn Crib, 1961 December 29 (Box 32, Folder 162)
    - Cades Cove: Sheep Grazing in Russell Field, 1930 October 19; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 85, Folder 3] (Box 32, Folder 163)
    - Cades Cove: John P. Cable Mill and Waiting Room, 1934 September 2 (Box 32, Folder 164)
    - Cades Cove: Mill Creek Falls, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 165)
    - Cades Cove: Cobweb on Fence, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 166)
    - Cades Cove: Daniel Bird Lawson Place, 1923 (Box 32, Folder 167)
    - Cades Cove: Cades Cove Loop Road, 1961 December 29 (Box 32, Folder 168)
    - Cades Cove: Dr. John Calvin Post Cemetery, 1995 November 1 (Box 32, Folder 169)
    - Cades Cove: Dr. John Calvin Post Home, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Cades Cove: Dr. John Calvin Post, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Cades Cove: Holly Tree at Dr. Calvin Post Home, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Cades Cove: 1922 Model T Ford Touring Car, circa 1920s (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Cades Cove: Forge Creek Canal to Mill Creek for Cable Mill, 1996 April 3-August 12 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Cades Cove: Typhoid Kills Family of Four (1898), 1996 April 3 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Cades Cove: Rocky Top, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Cades Cove: First Car in Cades Cove, 1914, 1968, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Cades Cove: Modena and William Feezell, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Cades Cove: Dr. Isaac Anderson, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Cades Cove: Reverend Isaac Anderson Gravesite, 1995 October 2 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Cades Cove: Joseph Estabrook, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Cades Cove: Abrams Falls, 1901 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Cades Cove: Fire Box Grate from John Abbott's Sawmill, 1996 March 16 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Cades Cove: Ruthie Myers McCalley, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Cades Cove: Alice and Rube Maynard, undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Cades Cove: Reverend John McCampbell Gravesite, 1995 May 16 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Cades Cove: Jonathan Tipton Gravesite, 1995 March 24 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Cades Cove: William Tipton Gravesite, 1995 March 24 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Cades Cove: Joe Gregory (owner of Gregory Cove), undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Cades Cove: Evan and Lina Brown Hawkins, undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Cades Cove: Peter Cable Gravesite, 1994 July 8 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Cades Cove: Tobacco Cutting, 1896 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Cades Cove: Lail Twins Gravesite, 1993 May 30 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Cades Cove: Inez McCauley, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Cades Cove: Spence Deadening Branch Road, 1936 May 26 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Cades Cove: Daniel Bird Lawson (1827-1905), undated (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Cades Cove: Lafayette Chambers Family, circa 1907 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Cades Cove: Tipton Boys Going Hunting, undated (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Cades Cove: USGS Survey Tower on Thunderhead Mountain (5530'), 1933 June 3-4 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Cades Cove: Long Hair Sam Burchfield (Moonshiner), circa 1910 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Cades Cove: Moonshine Still, undated (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Cades Cove: Jane Gibson Russell, undated (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Cades Cove: James R. D. Feezell (1839-1915), circa 1860s (Box 33, Folder 34)